hi!! mondai: hitori to futari docchi ga suteki?
Hi!! 問題: ひとりとふたりどっちが素敵？
Hi!! Here's a question:
Alone or together, which one is more wonderful?
(hai! oh~ let's go)
(はい！Oh~ Let's Go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go)
colorful mawaridasu watashi no shourai
colorful 回り出す私の将来
Colorfully, my future starts to spin.
dokomade hanasouka? minai furi? (nande)
どこまで話そうか?見ないふり？（なんで）
How long do we intend to just talk?
And pretend to not see each other? (Why?)
ah soo, ookina sekai wa kibun de hirogaru
あっそー、大きな世界は気分で広がる
Ah yes, the wide world expands, depending upon my feelings.
kyou mo daisuki (suki)
今日もだいすき（すき）
I love you today, as well. (Love!)
hontou ni daisuki
本当にだいすき
I really do love you.
watashi no baka (baka) hoshi no kazu yori mo baka da
わたしのバカ（バカ）星の数よりもバカだっ
My idiot (idiot!) So much more stupid than there are stars in the sky.
sunao ni narezu ni
素直になれずに
I had a dream, in which I walked together with you...
kimi to aruku yume wo mita (hai)
君と歩く夢を見た（はい）
being my honest self.
gomen ne datte! koi to shiranakattan da
ごめんね だって!恋としらなかったんだ
I'm sorry, but it's just... I hadn't known it to be love then.
kotaete kimi to
答えって 君と
Answer me this: You and
nazo tasu watashi wa
?+私=
something unknown plus me equals
mugen no jump!! (hai! oh~ let's go)
無限のJUMP!! (はい！Oh~ Let's GO!)
an infinite jump!! (Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
(hai! hands up)
（はい！Hands Up!)
(Yes! Hands up!)
(hai! all right)
(はい！All Right!)
(Yes! All right!)